{"data":[{"question":"She is _____ the housework.","a":"making","b":"having","c":"doing","d":"to do","answer":"3","explain":"\n- 'Do' is often used when referring to work of any kind. \n- Be + V_ing: Continuous tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They are going to ______ an exercise.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- There are a number of standard expressions that take the verb 'do'.For example: Do an exercise; Do a favor... \n- Going to + Verb infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I _____ the washing up yesterday.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 'Do' is used when someone performs an action, activity or task \n- Simple past tense: do- did","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm going to _____ my hair.","a":"make","b":"do","c":"doing","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Do someone's hair: Create some change to hair: style, color... \n- Going to + Verb infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"My mother ______ the ironing.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 'Do' is used when someone performs an action, activity or task \n- Simple past tense: Do - Did","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you _____ last night? I went to the cinema.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"did","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n-'Do' is used  to refer action, activity or task\n- Question of past tense: Did+ Subject + Verb infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We are going to ______ a long journey.","a":"made","b":"make","c":"do","d":"did","answer":"2","explain":"\n- There are a number of standard expressions that take the verb 'make'\n- Going to + Verb infinitive\nExample: Make a journey; make a mess; make friends...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She is going to ______ her job.","a":"do","b":"have","c":"make","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n-'Do' is often used when referring to work of any kind. \n- Example: do homework ; do your job \n- Going to + Verb infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"These children haven't _____ their homework.","a":"done","b":"made","c":"doing","d":"making","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do is often used when referring to work of any kind.\u00a0Example: do homework ; do your job \n- Present perfect tense: Do- done","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't ______ my homework on Saturday morning,","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do is often used when referring to work of any kind. \n- Example: do homework ; do your job \n- Negative structure of simple past tense: Didn't + Verb infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}